{
    "subject": "resource/Sam_Kinison",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Satire",
    "human_readable": "Sam Kinison is a Satire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7970466017723083,
            "question": "What were some common themes explored in Sam Kinison's satire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.514828622341156,
            "question": "What is Satire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5137454867362976,
            "question": "What type of performer was Sam Kinison?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4617207944393158,
            "question": "Who were some of Sam Kinison's influences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45568186044692993,
            "question": "Was Sam Kinison known for his humor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3387501835823059,
            "question": "What comedic style did Sam Kinison use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2873952388763428,
            "question": "What made Sam Kinison's performances unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23387891054153442,
            "question": "How did Sam Kinison use humor in his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22968925535678864,
            "question": "What impact did Sam Kinison have on comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22102570533752441,
            "question": "Did Sam Kinison's work often involve social commentary?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sam Kinison is a Satire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4364_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Sam Kinison have on comedy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4364_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Sam Kinison use humor in his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4364_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What made Sam Kinison's performances unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4364_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4364_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provided contain information about Sam Kinison as a stand-up comedian, detailing his style of humor and impact on comedy. However, there is no mention or implication that he was involved in satire specifically; the context indicates his work was more aligned with politically incorrect and intense humor rather than satire."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Sam Kinison is a real person and not a satire. He was an American stand-up comedian and actor known for his intense, harsh, and politically incorrect humor.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context describes Kinison as a comedian known for his intense, loud, and politically incorrect humor.  There's no mention of him using satire as a primary comedic tool.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Sam Kinison was actually a Pentecostal preacher before pursuing a career in comedy, which suggests that his work as a comedian was likely not satirical, but rather an expression of his own intense and humorous personality.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Sam Kinison was described as a stand-up comedian known for his intense, harsh, and politically incorrect humor. There is no information suggesting he was a satirist specifically. His comedic style, characterized by sensitive subjects and a bold approach, does not align with the term \"satire,\" which typically involves using humor to criticize or comment on society or human behavior in a more indirect manner.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}